《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."
是真的嗎
That true?
你想幫忙
You wanna help?
-是的  -好
- I do. - Okay.
我們要做好準備  我們必須反抗
We have to get ready. We have to fight.
是的
We do.
我們給你找到槍  然后一起戰斗
we get you the guns, we fight together.
-說同意  -同意
- Say yes. - Yes.
他們在外面  所以我要跟你去
They're out there, so I'm gonna be there with you.
我們要去
We are.
買一送一
Package deal.
你必須給我搞些東西來
You have to get me something.
刀  槍
A knife, a gun...
用這個就行  這是毒藥
This will do it. It's a poison.
官方合作
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
□|
創意
周邊
我愛美劇
■
52meiju.taobao.com
淘
●
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十五集』
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻譯     冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
翻譯     小酸奶 小僵僵 蘑菇 送小孩
親愛的
Hey, darlin'.
校對     冰藍吃涼皮  小孩吃夾饃
醒醒
Wake up.
親愛的  醒醒
Hey, darlin'. Wake up.
時間軸     濤濤  倉鼠  知之
怎么了  我們需要...
What is it? Do we need to --
不用  暫時沒事
No, no, no. We're okay for now.
后期     吉吉喝冰峰  拉圖吃泡饃
總監     送小孩餓了
你也下午好
Well, good afternoon to you.
你來了
You're here.
是啊
Yeah.
現在見到你  我渾身舒服
And I'm feelin' all kinds of glad to see you right now.
他們回來了嗎
Are they back?
還沒
Not yet.
我知道你最近上夜班  今晚也是
I know you were pullin' late shift, and you wanna tonight,
所以我不想吵醒你
so I didn't want to wake you up.
瑪姬有麻煩了
Maggie's in trouble.
什么
What?
孩子出了問題
Something with the baby.
瑞克要帶她去找山頂寨的醫生
Rick's taking her to the doctor at Hilltop.
他還不知道  但我要跟他去
He doesn't know it yet, but I'm going with him.
我只是
I just...
我知道我們才剛開始
I know we just started this,
-但我希望你...  -別
- but I wanted you to -- Don't.
別什么
"Don't" what?
別走
Don't go.
歡迎來到你余生的第一天  薩沙
Welcome to the first day of the rest of your life, Sasha.
你今天要幫我確保一切回到正軌
You are gonna help make sure things get back on track today.
你聰明性感  尊嚴高尚
You are smart, hot as hell, dignified as shit,
眼里容不得蠢貨
and you don't suffer one goddamn fool.
沒人想看你死
No one's gonna wanna watch you die.
我就不想
I don't wanna see that.
所以你沒必要死
So you don't have to.
但總得有人死
But someone does.
最多幾個人
Maybe a couple others -- tops.
但你不用死  大部分人也不用死
But not you and not most people.
我們要解決一些問題
We are gonna help solve some shit.
盡情吃吧
Tuck in.
今天是個大日子
Big day.
你需要我做什么
What do you need from me?
看著我
Look at me.
為什么
Why?
因為我想阻止這一切
'Cause I want it stopped.
我要尼根死
I want Negan dead.
那你為什么不殺他
So why don't you kill him?
我一個人做不到
Can't just be me.
他們都是尼根
They're all Negan.
你謀殺的那個女孩
That girl you murdered...
她有名字
She had a name.
她叫丹妮斯  是一名醫生
Her name was Denise, and she was a doctor.
她救助了很多人
And she helped people.
我瞄的不是她
I wasn't aiming for her.
動手  動手
Do it. Do it.
你想這樣結束
You wanna end it this way...
隨便你
You go ahead.
我很抱歉  真的
I'm sorry. I am.
我知道你很想
I know you want to.
他可能只是來打探你是否在這里的
He could just be here to see if you were here.
我們不能信任他
We can't trust him.
我曾是他的人
He owned me.
但不再是了
But not anymore.
我過去做的事
What I did,
都是為了某個人
I was doing it for someone else.
她最近跑掉了
She just got away.
所以我來了
So now I'm here.
那你是為了她嗎
So are you because of her?
動手啊
Do it!
你還有另一個選擇
There's another choice.
達里爾
Daryl.
-達里爾  你認識她  -尼根信任我
- Daryl, you knew her. - Negan trusts me.
我們可以合作  我們可以阻止他
We can work together, we can stop him.
你認識之前的我  也認識現在的我
You knew me then, and you know me now.
你知道我沒有撒謊
You know I'm not lying.
我沒有
I'm not.
動手啊
Do it.
動手
Do it!
他們抓住了薩沙  如果她還活著的話
They have Sasha, if she's even alive.
你為什么不早說
Why didn't you say something?
他可能是我們救回她的唯一機會
He could be our only chance to get her back.
因為我不信任他
Because I don't trust him.
但我信任達里爾
But I trust Daryl.
尼根馬上就要來了
Negan's coming soon.
明天
Tomorrow.
大概會來三輛卡車
Three trucks probably.
他和二十名救世軍
20 saviors and him.
我可以拖住他們
I can slow them down,
弄些樹把路擋住
bring some trees down in the road,
為你們爭取一點準備的時間
buy a little time for you guys to get ready.
假如你們能把他們干掉  我們就起了個好頭
If you can take them out, that's where we start.
你們殺了他們之后  我會發消息到救世堂
You kill them, I'll radio back to the sanctuary.
救世堂
The sanctuary?
尼根的住處
Where negan lives.
他們是這么叫的
That's what they call it.
我會發消息給他們  告訴他們一切順利
I can radio back to them and say everything's okay.
你們把卡車開回去
You drive the trucks back,
我可以領著你們直搗黃龍
and I can lead you right inside,
假如計劃得好  我們能把殘黨都干掉
and, with the right plan, we can wipe out the rest.
再去看看你們的朋友是否還活著
Check to see if your friend's still alive.
然后我們把工人拉攏到我們這邊
Then, we get the workers on our side,
增加人數
build our numbers up,
然后一個個哨站殺過去  結束這一切
and go from outpost to outpost and end this.
繼續說
Keep talking.
我們剛挑起了大戰
We just started it -- the whole thing.
假如他在撒謊  我會慢慢折磨死他
If he's lyin', I'm gonna kill him real slow.
等這一切結束了
When this is done,
我才不管他是不是悔過了
I don't give a damn if he's sorry.
我會殺了那個混蛋的
I will kill that son of a bitch.
假如他在撒謊
If he's lying,
我們早已完了
this is already over.
我得走了
Oh, I gotta go.
事實上  我覺得我們可以...
Fact is, I figured we'd --
我做了一個夢
I had a dream.
你...
You...
你夢到我了嗎
You had a dream about me?
你死了
You died.
計劃就是這樣
That's the plan.
這就是我需要你做的事
That's what I need from you.
你出來的時候  別吱聲
And when you come out, not a peep.
他們會投降  假如他們還沒投降的話
They will stand down, if they haven't already.
然后  露西爾會殺掉三個人
And then, Lucille here, well, she gets her three,
然后我們帶著全新的認知繼續前行
and we move forward with a new understanding.
你是在...你是在逗我嗎
Are you -- are you shitting me?
那是真的眼淚嗎
Is that real?
我可以配合  但沒必要殺人
I can do it, but no one has to die.
你錯了
You are wrong.
懲罰...
Punishment --
沒它什么都做不成
Can't do anything without that.
我們擁有的一切都是建立在懲罰之上的
Punishment is how we built everything we have.
你以為我會坐視你...
You think I'm gonna sit here and let you...
當心點
Careful!
我做什么輪不到你管
You are not letting me do anything.
沒必要死人
No one has to die.
好吧
Okay.
這樣如何
How about this?
一個
One.
只死一個
Just one.
我本來打算選三個
I mean, I was gonna pull three outta the pool,
但只殺一個
but just one,
專門為了你
and just for you.
好
Okay.
只用死一個人
Just one person has to die.
你真是把我玩弄于股掌之間
You got me wrapped around your little finger.
知道嗎
You know that?
這跟男女無關
And it's not a man woman thing.
我是說  就算你有根老二
I mean, if you had a dick,
我還是會有這種感覺的
I would still have these feelings.
45分鐘后出發
We roll out in 45.
我們沒爭取到海邊旅館  但我們有她們的槍
So we don't have Oceanside, but we have their guns.
而尼根手里有薩沙
Negan has Sasha.
達里爾希望我們相信德懷特
Daryl wants us to trust Dwight.
瑞克希望我們留在這以防不測
Rick wants us to stay here in case things go wrong
這樣還有另一手牌可打
so there's another card to play,
另一個救世軍以為受他們控制的安全之處
another safe place the Saviors think they control.
但他不知道格雷戈里已經離開了
But he doesn't know that Gregory's gone...
也許他告訴了他們一些事
That maybe he's telling them things,
會讓他們改變想法
that'll make them think something else.
這些都是會發生的
And it's all about to happen.
你在考慮領導山頂寨反抗
You're thinking of leading the Hilltop over there to fight.
是的
I am.
如果尼根發現他們在計劃什么
If Negan finds out they're planning something,
他們就需要幫助了
they're gonna need help,
雖然那些拾荒者都站在他們那邊
Even with those scavengers on their side.
你必須現在就決定
Well, you'd have to decide right now,
這是個艱難的決定
and it's a very tough decision.
你笑什么
Why are you smiling?
因為我很高興你是為我們做決定的人
'cause I'm glad you're the one making it for us.
該怎么決定
How do I?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道你能做出決定
I just know you can.
我來照顧她
Let me take her.
你拿著這個
You take this.
端起槍
Guns up, now.
怎么回事  他已經死了
What the hell? He's dead.
怎么了
What is it?
以前見過這個
We've seen this before.
跟以前一樣
Same ones.
伙計  你沒事吧
Dude, you okay?
-你要一個人伏擊他們嗎  -對
- You're gonna ambush them on your own? - Yeah.
現在不可以一個人單干
Going alone doesn't work for this.
我可以
It works for me.
你殺過他們的人了嗎
Have you killed any of them?
因為如果你殺過  并且被他們發現了
Because if you have and they've found out,
他們也許會認為是神之國干的
they may think it was the Kingdom,
我們會失去有利條件
and we lose our advantage.
這是行尸的血
It's from walkers.
我們能把路障移開嗎
Can we move them aside?
你欲抹殺從前的自己嗎
Do you seek to extinguish everything of who you were?
沒有  但是
I don't seek it, but...
我不知所從
I'm stuck.
你想讓救世軍們死嗎
You want the Saviors dead?
-摩根  -是的
- Morgan. - Yes, I do.
停止你的愚行
Cease this folly.
加入我的軍隊
Accompany my regiment.
救世軍好似多頭巨龍
The Saviors are a dragon with many heads,
兵多將廣
their numbers legion.
我們必須聯合盟友與之一戰
We must seek allies in this endeavor.
那是本杰明的盔甲
That's Benjamin's armor.
你穿著是為了保護自己  還是為了紀念他
Do you wear it to serve you, or do you wear it in his honor?
摩根
Morgan...
最新海外影視劇下載
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
你沒有走投無路
You are not stuck.
加入我們的旅程  結為盟友
Join us on this journey to create an alliance.
和我們一起戰斗
Fight with us,
我們會打敗他們  不會再讓別人
and we shall defeat them so that no one will suffer
被他們玩弄蹂躪
under their capricious malevolence ever again.
我們為了逝者
And we start once more for the fallen...
為了神之國
for the Kingdom...
為了勝利的榮耀再次戰斗
...for the glory of victory.
你們為何而戰
What you fight for.
不是為了這個地方  而是為了彼此
Not the place -- the people, each other.
現在你們也是我們的一員了
You're a part of that now.
我們只拿  不費心  這是我們的方式
We take. We don't bother --our way.
也許該換種方式了
Maybe another way.
你男人嗎
Yours?
我們是在一起
Yeah, we're together.
我過后要睡他
I lay with him after.
你介意嗎
You care?
-該回去干活了  -是啊
- We should get back to work. - Yeah.
你覺得是他們干的嗎
Think this was them?
我想過
Crossed my mind.
我們有后備計劃
We got a plan "B."
恕我直言
If I might be so bold...
這突然的阻礙讓我
this unexpected stoppage has given me
有機會能好好考慮一下
the chance for an exhaustive mull.
根據現在的嚴峻形勢
Now, given the loaded circumstances
還有潛在傷亡和資源消耗
and potential for casualties and resource expenditure,
你能不能給我個機會
I was wondering if you would give me the opportunity
去勸降他們  讓他們冷靜
to attempt to slow their jets and cool their roll.
你以前用過這種槍嗎
You shoot one of these before?
很好
Good.
擔心嗎
Worry?
不
No.
很好
Good.
-我去另一個塔  -為什么
- I'll be on the next one over. - Why?
分頭行動視野更好
It's more sight lines if we split up.
我去
I'll go.
你確定嗎
You sure?
好吧
Okay.
我們會贏
We win.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道會發生什么事
You know what's gonna happen,
這會如何結束
How this is gonna end.
你知道會發生什么事
You know what's gonna happen,
這會如何結束
How this is gonna end.
我們要一起走出那扇門
We're gonna walk out that door together.
同甘共苦
We kick shit and eat snakes.
-我們就是這樣  -我們這次可以不管
- That's us. - We can sit this one out.
反正他們也需要我們留在這
They need us here, anyway.
瑞克說要準備好戰斗
Rick said to get ready for a fight.
我怎么死的
How'd I die?
我們當時在沙灘上
We were at the beach.
是在災變前
It was before.
你被水卷了進去
You got pulled under...
沒能出來
And you didn't come back up.
我試著去找你  但是你不見了
I was trying to find you, but you were gone.
然后  我開始溺水
And then, I started to drown.
我討厭沙灘
I hate the beach.
穿著橡膠衣玩一天
End of the day in a wet suit?
回到車上的每一步
It's like you're sandblasting your nutsack
蛋都像在被噴砂
every single step you take back to the car.
還好今天不去海邊
Luckily, the seaside ain't on the agenda today.
只是守衛和趕路
Just security and some road to chew.
好嗎  來吧
All right? So, come on.
-我們去幫瑪姬  -亞伯拉罕
- Let's go help Maggie. - Abraham.
什么
What?
這里需要我們
They can use us here.
就這一次  我們不逞英雄
Just once, we sit one out.
-別人...  -應該是我們
- Someone else -- - it should be us.
瑪姬應該靠自己
Maggie's gotta take care of maggie.
吃過敏藥的事
Have you, uh, changed your mind
你有沒有改變主意
about taking that allergy medication?
-有  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
我覺得你會適應這個地方的
I think you'll get adjusted to the place, sinus-wise.
不會的
No, I won't.
不像你
Not like you.
每個人都有自己的出路
Everyone has a way out.
別因為我的選擇批判我
Don't go and yuck my yum for takin' mine,
順便說  你也選的一樣
which, I may add, is the same as yours now.
如果今天有人死  都是自己選的
If people die today, it's 'cause of the choices they made.
是啊  確實如此
Yeah. It is.
我們在這里做什么
Why are we here?
等這個
For this.
羅西塔
Rosita.
就位
Get into position.
我給你信號
I'll signal you.
晲S問題吧
And the wall's gonna hold?
沒問題
It'll hold.
你們已被包圍
All points are covered.
所有意外都在考慮內
Every contingency is already met.
我帶著真相前來
I come armed with two barrels of the truth.
大考將至  而我給你們帶來了小抄
A test is upon you, and I'm giving out the cheat sheet.
你們好
H-hello.
我前來勸降  因為我知道你們通情達理
I come salved with the hope that it is my dropped knowledge that you heed.
你們沒有選擇余地
Options are zero to none.
忠誠服從是唯一出路
Compliance and fealty are your only escape.
說白了  你們可生  亦或死
Bottom-lining it -- you may thrive, or you may die.
我衷心希望是前者
I sincerely wish for the former
為了所有人著想
For everyone's sake.
你們已經完全暴露了
The jig is up and in full effect.
你們投降嗎  瑞克
Will you comply, rick?
尼根在哪
Where's Negan?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
不
No.
我們會贏
We win.
你聽過叫瑞克的小傻瓜
You ever hear the one about the stupid little prick named rick
以為自己本事大卻一無所知
who thought he knew shit but didn't know shit
害自己在乎的人被殺光的故事嗎
and got everyone he that gave a shit about killed?
說的就是你
It's about you.
你們最好都把槍放下
You're all gonna wanna put your guns down now.
所有人都別放下槍
No one drops anything.
我們說好的
We had a deal.
塔米爾去拿船上物資
Tamiel came for the boat things.
跟蹤了奪走物資的人
Followed ones who took.
做了筆更好的交易
Made a better deal.
你一而再  再而三地逼我  瑞克
You push me, and you push me. And you push me, Rick.
你剛才想炸了我們是吧
You just tried to blow us up, right?
你想弄死我和我的人  我懂
I mean, I get me, my people.
但是尤金呢
But Eugene?
他可是你的人
He's one of yours.
他做了那事之后  洗心革面了
And after what he did -- he stepped up.
你們這些人
You people...
真是禽獸
are animals.
上帝給了你們啟示
Universe gives you a sign, and you just
你們卻回了個中指  捅了他的菊花
shove your finger right up its ass.
德懷特  西蒙  快去
Dwight, Simon, chop-chop.
好吧  你們不喜歡尤金了
So, you don't like Eugene anymore.
但你們肯定喜歡薩沙
You guys gotta like Sasha.
我也喜歡她
I do, too.
為了方便你們  我把她裝在這里面了
Got her right here packaged for your convenience,
毫發無損
alive and well.
我帶來了她  就不用殺了你們所有人了
Now, I brought her so I wouldn't have to kill all of you,
但不把你們都殺了  事情會變得很復雜
and not killing all of you could get complicated.
我知道里面還有很多武器  瑞克
See, I know there's a lot of firepower left in there, Rick.
我的要求很簡單
So I'm gonna make this simple.
我要你們想方設法積攢來的所有槍
I want all the guns you've managed to scrape up.
是的  這個我也知道
Yep, I know about those, too.
我要你們剩下的所有檸檬粉
I want every last grain of lemonade you got left.
我還要你選一個人
I want a person of your own choosing...
送給露西爾
For Lucille.
達里爾
Daryl --
我得要回我的達里爾
Ooh, I gotta get me my Daryl back.
我看到你了
I see you.
還有臺球桌
And the pool table
全部臺球桿和巧粉
and all the pool cues and chalk.
我現在就要
And I want it now
不然薩沙就得死
or Sasha dies,
然后你們所有人都得死
And then all of you.
大概吧
Probably.
行了  瑞克
C'mon, Rick.
我把她裝在棺材里帶來
Just because I brought her in a casket
不意味著她就得死在里面
doesn't mean she has to leave in it.
你知道嗎
You know what?
你遜斃了  瑞克
You suck ass, Rick.
真的
You really do.
我不想殺她
I don't want to have to kill her,
但這正是你逼我要做的事情
but that's exactly what you're gonna make me do.
讓我看看她
Let me see her.
好吧  給我點時間
All right. Just give me a second.
我也許得跟她說說現在什么情況了
I might have to get her up to speed.
在棺材里可什么都聽不到
You can't hear shit inside this thing.
薩沙
Sash.
你絕對不會相信這破事的
You're not gonna believe this crap.
感覺很真實
It felt real.
像是失去了這一切
Like we lost this.
而我們才剛剛開始
And this just started.
-走吧  -等等
- C'mon. - Wait.
我喜歡你看穿我的樣子
I like the way you call bullshit.
所以這次讓我來幫幫你吧
So let me return the favor.
接下來你要跟我說的是
The next thing you're gonna tell me
你會去  這樣我就可以留下
is that you'll go and that I can stay.
因為我知道  你自己也不想說出
Because I know you didn't like hearing yourself just say
"瑪姬應該靠自己"這種話
that, "Maggie's gotta take care of Maggie."
我知道這句話會縈繞在你腦中
I know those words are gonna choke in your ears
很久很久
a good, long while
你會因為僅僅有這念頭而做出補償
and you're gonna wanna make up for even thinking that.
我說得對嗎
Am I right?
對
Yeah.
我們為別人置生死于度外
We lay our big meaties across the chopping block ahead of someone else's.
總是為別人
It's always for someone else.
我們都知道  如果我們要死
Both of us know, if we're gonna kick,
那最好死得有意義
there sure as hell better be a point to it.
所以或許我們覺得這一切都是有意義的
So maybe we feel there was a-a point to all of this.
自始至終
Alpha to omega.
不管是在戰場  還是在海邊
Whether it's on the battlefield or the beach
還是別的什么地方
or somewhere out there today.
瑪姬
Maggie --
她懷著未來
She's carrying the future.
你說得對
You're right.
我就知道會這樣
I knew how this was gonna end.
走吧
C'mon.
為別人冒生命危險
Layin' your ass on the line for someone else,
為他們掃除障礙
Tearin' it to shreds for 'em --
你以前說過
You said it before.
這才叫活著
Oh, my, that is living.
你真是個傻瓜
You're an idiot.
我從沒說過我不是
I never said otherwise.
去那里要幾個小時  對嗎
A couple hours to get there, right?
至少吧
At least.
路上也許障礙重重
Might be a circuitous and janky route.
鑒于他們在謀反  道路很可能被監視了
With what they're planning, they could be watching the roads.
"他們在謀反"
"What they're planning."
沒錯
That's right.
我在市集拿的  存滿了歌
Got it in the marketplace. It's chock-full.
在途中恐怕無法交談
Doubt conversation will be on tap for the commute.
盡管我是個自私的懦夫
And though I am a selfish coward,
我有時也會為別人著想
I do tend to think of other people on occasion.
請收下我的饋贈吧
Please take it with my compliments.
我真心希望我能做好人
I truly wish I measured up.
你依然可以  尤金
You still can, Eugene.
我不會放棄
I'm not giving up.
不會放棄你
Not on you.
天啊  你不用躺在那玩意兒里面過去
Jesus, you don't have to take the trip in the thing.
我想休息一下
I could use the rest.
不是吧
No shit?
是的
Yeah.
我只想睡覺
I just want to go to sleep.
給我一小瓶水就行了
I just need a little bottle of water, and I'm fine.
阿拉特
Arat?
聽著
Listen...
我知道這有多難
I know how tough this is.
我很感激
And I appreciate it.
該死  你真了不得
Damn, you are something else.
正在播放
《總有一天  我們都會自由》
唐尼·海瑟威
薩沙
Sash.
你絕對不會相信這破事的
You're not gonna believe this crap.
我的媽呀
Holy goddamn!
快走
Go! Go!
別
No.
親愛的  該死
Aah! honey, god damn it!
那就后備計劃吧
Plan "B" It is!
跪下  快點
Down. Now.
我們可以重新做筆交易
We can make another deal.
我說了跪下
I said, down.
又見面了
Hello again.
跪下  不然再吃一槍
Down. Or again.
靠  瑞克
Well, shit, Rick.
你就不能老實跟著我們嗎
You just couldn't stick with us, huh?
非要找這些撿破爛的臟人
You had to go with these filthy garbage people?
無意冒犯
No offense.
說好了是12個  對嗎
Deal is for 12, yes?
10個
10.
人才是資源
People are a resource.
12個
12.
10個
10.
瑞克
Rick.
這會讓你難過的
This is just gonna make you sad.
心碎
Broken.
你會希望你死了
You're gonna wish you were dead.
我喜歡鬧著玩
I like having fun.
真的
I do.
但也許你覺得對你朋友做出那種事的人不是我了
But maybe you think that the guy that did what he did to your friends wasn't me,
以為那不過是某種作秀
like that was some sort of a put-on,
以為我不是拿著大棒的人
like I'm not the guy with the bat --
只是個給你孩子做意面的人
I'm just the guy that makes your kid spaghetti.
靠
Oh, shit.
也許這怪我
Maybe this is on me.
也許這全都怪我
Maybe this is all on me.
我必須糾正錯誤
I gotta make it right.
我猜又要重來一遍了
I guess I gotta start all over again.
必須告訴你  瑞克
I gotta tell you, Rick,
假如我有孩子
if I had a kid,
我希望他跟你孩子一樣
I'd want him to be just like your kid,
所以這就更難了
which makes this so much harder.
你贏不了的
You're not gonna win.
卡爾
Carl.
已經結束了
It is over.
何不用你的獨眼
Why don't you point your one ball
看看那邊  感受一下
up the street there and take it all in?
我們會贏
We'll win!
我們會活
We live!
是我們
We're the ones!
我們
Us!
你剛失去了某個重要的人  就在剛剛
You just lost somebody important to you right now -- like, just now.
老天啊
Jesus.
時機剛好
That is timing.
瑞克
Well, Rick...
這是你選的
you chose this.
我真不知道我還能怎么警告你
I truly don't know what more I could've done to warn you.
而且這不是警告了
And this isn't a warning.
這是懲罰
This is punishment.
我現在要殺了卡爾
I'm gonna kill Carl now.
我會狠狠地  重重地揮一棒
I'm gonna make it one nice, hard swing,
試著一擊斃命  因為我喜歡他
try to do it in one because I like him.
我只想讓你把這個念頭放進腦子里
I just want you to put that in your brain
細細回味一下
and roll it around for a minute.
我會殺了卡爾  然后露西爾
I'm gonna kill Carl, and then Lucille here,
她會砸爛你的雙手
she's gonna take your hands.
你可以就在我面前做
You can do it right in front of me.
你可以砸爛我的雙手
You can take my hands.
我已經告訴過你了
I told you already --
我會殺了你
I'm gonna kill you.
你們所有人
All of you.
也許不在今天  也許不在明天
Maybe not today, maybe not tomorrow...
但沒有什么能改變這點
but nothing is gonna change that --
沒有什么
Nothing.
你們已經死了
You're all already dead.
靠
Damn.
瑞克
Wow, Rick.
好吧
Okay.
你說了我可以做
You said I could do it.
滅了救世軍和他們的同伙
End these Saviors and their accomplices!
亞歷山大不會陷落  不在今天
Alexandria will not fall, not on this day!
方形陣  第三隊  上
Phalanx out, third group, now!
上  我們掩護你們
Move up! Now we got your backs!
他媽的一頭老虎啊
A goddamn tiger!
那寡婦沒死  活蹦亂跳的
That widow is alive, guns a-blazin'!
你嘗到了嗎  西蒙  這就是吃屎的滋味
You taste that, Simon? That is the taste of shit!
他們撤退了
They're falling back.
愛德華多  伯蒂  去房屋之間
Eduardo, Bertie, between the houses --
掩護大門
Cover the gate!
走
Let's go.
現在收尾
Now we finish this!
上
Now!
拉
Pull! ?
米瓊恩
Michonne.
Michonne. ?
你還活著
Oh, you're alive.
我們...
We -- W-We're...
We're...
我知道  我知道
I know. I know. ?
我知道
I know.
我們活下來了
We are.
我們會活下去
We will.
準備已就緒
Getting preparations in place.
所有人都是藍色警戒
Everyone's on "Blue level."
只要你下令  他們就出發
You say the word, they're ready to go.
很好
That's good.
你覺得她怎么會死在棺材里
How the hell do you think she wound up dead in that box?
最可能的原因是油布
My, um, best possible posit fingers the tarp.
棺材被封得嚴嚴實實
That sealed up said box good and tight.
沒氧氣了
She ran out of air.
也許吧
Maybe.
那么
So...
我們要開戰了
we are going to war!
遵命
Yes, sir!
你覺得薩沙是一個人做到的嗎
Do you think Sasha did that herself?
我不知道怎么做到的  但我知道她做到了
I don't know how, but I know she did.
她給了我們機會  你給了我們機會
She gave us a chance. You did.
你選擇過來是正確的
You made the right decision to come.
這選擇很早以前就做了
The decision was made a long time ago,
在我們大家相識之前
before any of us knew each other,
當我們還是在街上擦肩而過的陌生人時
when we were all strangers who would have just passed each other on the street
在世界結束之前
before the world ended.
現在我們對彼此意味著一切
And now we mean everything to each other.
你遇到了麻煩  你陷入了困境
You were in trouble. You were trapped.
格倫不認識你  但他救了你
Glenn didn't know you, but he helped you.
他為你冒了生命危險
He put himself in danger for you.
這是一切的源頭
And that started it all --
從亞特蘭大  到我爸爸的農場
From Atlanta, to my daddy's farm,
到監獄
to the prison,
到這里
to here...
到此時此刻
to this moment now...
我們不再是陌生人
not as strangers --
而是家人
as family...
當時不知道
因為格倫那天選擇救了你
because Glenn chose to be there for you that day
很久很久以前
a long time ago.
而那個選擇改變了一切
That was the decision that changed everything.
這是你們倆發起的
It started with both of you,
然后不斷壯大
and it just grew...
如今我們所有人
to all of us...
為彼此做出犧牲
to sacrifice for each other...
承受苦難
to suffer and stand,
去哀悼  去給予
to grieve, to give,
去愛  去生活
to love, to live...
去為彼此而戰
to fight for each other.
格倫做出了那個選擇  瑞克
Glenn made the decision, Rick.
我不過是在追隨他的腳步
I was just following his lead.
紀念伯尼·懷特森(1948-2017)
[注:驚悚漫畫大師  沼澤怪物之父
作品影響了多位《行尸》劇組成員
與癌癥抗爭多年后辭世]